Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
HE DESPIRE!
THIS IS WHERE YOU LOST!
Asta dealt Veto a massive, full-body blow that sent him flying.
Take that, jerk!
Though Vettos seemed to be down, the fight wasn't over yet.
I'm taking you with me, all of you!
In fact, I'm going to blow this entire temple away!
Just then.
I miss anything?
Hey there, you dumbbells. How's it going?
Captain Yami!
Fueled by his injured, weary squad's admiration and hope, Yami struck a massive blow of his own.
However strong your magic might be now, it doesn't matter.
Dark magic.
Dark gold.
Dimension Slash!
Thanks for toughening up my squad.
Now goodbye, Mr. Despair.
Watch from the sidelines a little longer. You're going to be my main dish.
You'll be steeped in delicious despair from having seen the deaths of all your friends.
Looks like you didn't make it to the main dish. Rest in peace.
No, I'm sorry. I, uh, I never despaired either.
Hold your hands specifically.
I'll like my hand in similarly to the theτ.
You can't talk too much.
This can be a radiation ר SMACK.
Be Oystered for many errands.
You can't stare at all right now.
If you don't talk too much.
Trying to walk too much.
Love her with someone living out, please look like I'm going to do theкая σk cooper Basic складâm笑
about our schreiben.
You can't speak language WHEN STAY الق
日本語字幕で視聴していた.
karşı离物語字幕 in Gamección.
南部字幕エクス , который IC MEDIRMOS、
ゲーム字幕 pessoal .
日本語字幕をご覧ください .
日本語字幕を解 kicks in.
ただだけど、もしこんなことが
it's back
it's
Oh, man.
This guy's pretty heavy.
Just hang in there.
We're gonna get you a healer as soon as we can.
There we go.
Oh, Manny!
Huh?
I'm not sensing that monster...
at all.
Captain Yami!
Careful.
Hey, we didn't ask for your help, you know.
I mean, you were a big help, but you could have shown up a little sooner.
Geez, what's with the attitude?
I've fallen for you all over again, Captain Yami.
What girl could resist such an incredible fighter?
Here you go, drink up!
Later.
I thought...
I was done for!
My life flashed before my eyes!
You were surprisingly useful in battle for once.
Thank you, sir!
Um, that was amazing, Captain!
I actually talked to him!
And who were you again?
You were mind-blowing out there!
Hey, fluffy sheep.
Captain.
It's over.
So can I go and see Marie now?
Take the hint.
This is where you tell me how great I am.
I can't believe you took him down with just one hint!
You're so awesome, Captain Yami!
I-
Yeah, I'm done now!
Leeches.
What's up, geezer?
Captain Yami Sukahiro, and all you black bulls!
By defeating the Eye of the Midnight Sun, you have indisputably won the game!
And...
For saving the Underwater Temple and its people, you have my gratitude!
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
As High Priest, please allow me to grant you a reward!
Anything in my power!
The only thing we won is what you originally promised us.
You said that you'd hand over the Magic Stone if we won your game.
Well, give it up.
What in the world is a Magic Stone?
Huh?
Come on, old man.
You know what I'm talking about.
You came to my temple to seek the Magic Stone, didn't you?
If you want it, you'll have to play a game with me first!
What are you senile now?
Oh, well, I only said that because I heard you all talking about it and I wanted competitors for my game.
So you really went through all this for some rock?
Okay.
And why is it so special?
Why, you little-
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
You wouldn't hurt a fragile old man, would you?
Peace!
It's been so long!
I haven't felt that pain since Saucy Village.
I was wondering where you'd gone off to, Nero.
Looks like you were busy finding the Magic Stone.
Good job!
So that's the Magic Stone.
You're more than welcome to take it with you as your reward.
Go on, don't be shy!
Trust me, we weren't planning to be.
All right.
Got it.
And now our mission's complete.
Listen up, gang.
Nice work.
Sir!
Now that I can finally relax, all my strength is kind of-
Master!
I don't even have a drop of magic left.
Same.
Me too.
I'm so hungry!
They're dropping like flies!
Come now!
We must see to restoring your magic and healing those wounds!
Restoring your magic and healing those wounds.
How could Vero have been defeated? It's unbelievable.
They've done it again. This will cause Ligt even more grief. I won't forgive them.
We must recover the magic stone and ensure that the eye of the Midnight Sun's dream is realized.
How ridiculous. We have to wait until Finral's magic is recovered to go back to the surface. Stupid good for nothing.
Hey, I'm right here.
I can't believe it, Gray. You're a cute little girl, not a big creepy guy.
I'm so embarrassed. Please don't look at me.
Quit staring at her like she's a piece of meat or I'll have to sew your eyes closed, you skis.
And as for you, Gray, you won't make it very long in this world if you're going to be that shy.
Yes, ma'am.
Maybe you could stand to be a little more shy, you shameless witch.
Oh, I'm sorry. Am I embarrassing the poor virgin street punk?
Who are you calling a punk, huh?
I sure hope I can get back to fighting soon.
I'm so hungry, I can't even keep my eyes open.
Look at the rest of us. You're lucky you're just hungry.
What's that?
Bored portly, how's it taste?
I can't believe I got taken out of the fight and missed my chance to show what I can really do.
Well, we did our best, but I guess we're just not at that level yet.
A banquet?
Thank you, Black Bulls!
You're all incredible!
You're the saviors of the Underwater Temple!
How can we ever thank you?
That was so amazing!
I can't freaking believe it.
People are actually thanking us.
The worst of the worst Magic Knight Squads.
Yeah, it's pretty cool, huh?
It makes me want to get a lot stronger.
What?
Well, okay then.
I'll get even stronger!
I'd like to see Marie more.
I want to work on being less shy.
Oh, wow! She is stunning!
And so is she!
Well, it sounds like someone's totally recovered.
It really is nice having somebody thank you.
I'm sorry, Kahono.
I couldn't stop him.
You're my friend, and I didn't save your voice.
Can you ever forgive me?
Quit being silly, Noelle.
Voice or not, you saved my life.
Thank you.
But I...
Your magic was amazing!
If it was, that's only because I had help from you.
Well, sure.
Feel free to thank me now.
One more thing.
I haven't given up on my dream.
I will recover and go ashore.
I'll sing again.
No matter how long it takes, I'll become an idol someday.
And once I am, you would better come and watch me perform.
Okay?
Kahono.
You better believe I'll come see you, and I expect you to save me a good seat.
Promise me?
I promise.
Uh, you should probably be getting some more rest, but I'll be back.
Thanks for visiting.
Okay, I'll see you later, then.
Oh, I didn't know you were awake.
What's up with you?
Your face is even goofier than usual.
She looked so beautiful when she cried.
And even more so when she smiled.
Is that who everyone's been talking about?
Is she the sea goddess?
I'm in love.
Alright.
My leg has to heal now.
I need to woo her with my dancing.
So, you'll introduce me?
Come on, sis.
Help me out here.
Yeah!
I'm getting back in the groove.
Something tells me Noelle's off the market.
Whoa!
Ow!
So many crazy, unexpected things happened on this mission, but at least we got the magic stone in the end.
Nero, where are you going?
Wait up, you stupid bird!
You can't just fly wherever you want to!
Honestly, if you get lost, don't come crying to me.
What's wrong?
What you need, kid?
I should have known you'd sense me here!
Guess my key gave me away.
I asked you a question.
Now give me an answer, or I'll mess you up.
Wah-ha-ha!
Well, um, it's just, since we're leaving tomorrow and all, I wanted to check the place out a bit.
I've been poking around here and there.
You some kind of explorer now?
Well, you find anything interesting?
Oh, uh, yeah, actually.
I found a fossil shaped like a shell, was nearly swallowed by this sea anemone, got absolutely swarmed by all these sea roaches.
Gross.
And there's these.
They were really pretty, and I thought, maybe...
You know, I can't forgive them for what they did.
Still, I don't really know what it might have been, but maybe something unforgivable happened to them, too.
And so now, they hate humans and only care about revenge.
Dreams and bombs.
What do humans know of those?
Don't speak such words to me, girl!
Oh, you've done it now, human.
You may think there's strength in numbers, but that's just an illusion.
You have no hope!
I won't lose to you, humans!
Your lives belong to me!
In the end, I think maybe he was the one who despaired the most.
Hey, kid, you're an idiot, right?
Huh?
I said you're an idiot, aren't you?
Answer me, or I'll mess you up.
Yes, I'm an idiot, Captain Yami, sir!
An idiot doesn't have to think too deep about that kind of stuff.
Got it!
Huh?
You just focus on following your dream.
That's it?
My dream?
For now, anyway.
I can't see it!
I can't pull my headband back up!
Come on, I've got two broken arms, remember?
Hey, Captain!
Where are you going, sir?
You can't just leave me here!
For now, all I have to do is follow my dream.
Huh.
My dream, except it's not just mine.
Check it out, you know!
I got a snazzy new grimoire!
Okay, it's a little beat up, but I'll treasure it all my life anyway!
I will!
I will repay my debt one day.
Asta, we made a promise.
Do you remember it?
So you want to be the Wizard King, too?
That means...
You know, Asta?
You are my rival!
I actually can't believe you remember it.
The way you've been acting lately, I was pretty sure you'd forgotten.
Like I'd be friendly with someone I consider my rival.
You showed me it was possible, gave me hope, that even though we're poor orphans,
commoners, we can still make something of ourselves in this world.
And to prove that?
To make Sister Lily and everybody else happy.
We'll fight to see who will be the Wizard King.
Whatever it takes.
Not yet.
I'm nowhere near as powerful as I need to be.
Yuno's got the lead for now.
The captain was totally right!
I'm just gonna follow my own dream!
Yeah, that's it!
My arms are gonna heal!
I'll get stronger than I've ever been!
And then I'll become the Wizard King!
Magic Knight!
Really fantastic!
Thank you!
How long are they gonna thank us for?
Sure are energetic.
Maybe too much.
Nothing wrong with a little gratitude, if you ask me.
And look at the ladies!
Beautiful!
Oh, good.
Go on, eat them!
Well, see ya.
And thanks for everything.
Please come back anytime.
You're always welcome here.
Yeah, come back!
Okay?
I'm the strongest of all the mages in the Underwater Temple, and I never got to show off my moves!
So, uh, how are the captured Midnight Sun minions holding up?
They're screaming a bunch, but they can't go anywhere, so I'm not really worried about it.
Man, that is a seriously strong binding spell you've got there.
Huh, guess I never crossed my mind.
Guess I never crossed my mind.
Just keep at it, alright?
I know your dreams will come true someday.
There's gotta be a spell that can heal your leg and your throat.
I'll work hard too, and get my arms all fixed up!
I'll be dancing on this leg again in no time.
Asta, thank you.
I'm never gonna give up either.
Okay, let's go.
Yes, sir!
Good.
I can finally go see Marie.
Um, thank you for everything!
See ya!
Bye-bye!
Later, guys!
Yeah!
Thanks for the food!
Take care!
Visit anytime!
Thanks again!
A?
flua
Avel-mu-ulah
To me, you know it, I'll touch it.
You know it, I'll touch it.
I'll touch it.
This is really what's a boy to do.
I'm not that talented, but these situations just seem to fall into my lap.
Captain Jack was actually crying, he was so moved.
Yes.
Haha.
Oh, I may be a tad drunk.
On my cell.
Don't get comfy just cause we got one mission done, we're moving right on to the next.
What?
I'm staying back at HQ?
Black Clover, page 51.
Proof of Rightness.
My magic's doing whatever it takes to hold down the fort.